<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Doc Nyc News Today</title>
	<atom:link href="https://watch.docnyc.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://watch.docnyc.net</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:16:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://watch.docnyc.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOCNYC5100.png</url>
	<title>Doc Nyc News Today</title>
	<link>https://watch.docnyc.net</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Live-action &#8216;Little Mermaid&#8217; debut makes box office waves</title>
		<link>https://watch.docnyc.net/live-action-little-mermaid-debut-makes-box-office-waves/</link>
					<comments>https://watch.docnyc.net/live-action-little-mermaid-debut-makes-box-office-waves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://watch.docnyc.net/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Disney&#8217;s live-action version of ‘The Little Mermaid’ netted the top spot at North American box offices on its opening weekend, over the United States&#8217; Memorial Day holiday, industry watcher Exhibitor Relations reported Sunday. The remake of the 1989 animated tale of an underwater princess who gives up her voice in pursuit of true love on land, starring pop singer Halle]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Disney&#8217;s live-action version of ‘The Little Mermaid’ netted the top spot at North American box offices on its opening weekend, over the United States&#8217; Memorial Day holiday, industry watcher Exhibitor Relations reported Sunday.</p>



<p>The remake of the 1989 animated tale of an underwater princess who gives up her voice in pursuit of true love on land, starring pop singer Halle Bailey and Melissa McCarthy, raked in $117.5 million in US and Canadian box offices and another $68 million internationally, Exhibitor Relations said.</p>



<p>Despite the number one spot, analyst David A Gross pointed out that the aquatic adventure&#8217;s debut does not represent the biggest opening weekend for a live-action Disney adaptation.</p>



<p>He recalled that 2019&#8217;s ‘The Lion King’ and 2017&#8217;s ‘Beauty and the Beast’ earned $191.8 million and $174.8 million respectively, over their opening weekends.</p>



<p>&#8220;During the last dozen years, Disney has built live-action remakes into a powerhouse phenomenon,&#8221; Gross wrote in the FranchiseRe newsletter.</p>



<p>Still, Ariel and friends were able to bump last week&#8217;s number one feature ‘Fast-X’ down to a distant number two, with Universal&#8217;s action film pulling in only $29.5 million in the Friday to Monday period.</p>



<p>That&#8217;s less than half of what the movie, part of the ‘Fast &amp; Furious’ franchise starring Vin Diesel, made during its opening weekend last week.</p>



<p>Disney&#8217;s ‘Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 3’ and Universal&#8217;s ‘The Super Mario Bros Movie’ were also knocked down one spot each from last weekend to take third and fourth places, making $25.3 million and $7.7 million.</p>



<p>In fifth place was Sony&#8217;s new action comedy ‘The Machine’, which earned $5.8 million and is based on US comedian Bert Kreischer&#8217;s stand-up routine.</p>



<p>Rounding out the top 10 were, ‘About My Father’ ($5.3 million), ‘Kandahar’ ($3 million), ‘You Hurt My Feelings’ ($1.8 million), ‘Evil Dead Rise’ ($1.2 million) and ‘Book Club: The Next Chapter’ ($1.2 million).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://watch.docnyc.net/live-action-little-mermaid-debut-makes-box-office-waves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Argentina World Cup winner Martinez confirms Bangladesh tour</title>
		<link>https://watch.docnyc.net/argentina-world-cup-winner-martinez-confirms-bangladesh-tour/</link>
					<comments>https://watch.docnyc.net/argentina-world-cup-winner-martinez-confirms-bangladesh-tour/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://watch.docnyc.net/?p=9</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Argentina’s World Cup winning goalkeeper Emiliano Martinez on Monday confirmed on Facebook that he will be visiting Bangladesh in July. Martinez wrote, “Hello Everybody, I will be doing my maiden trip to Indian subcontinent from 3rd July to 5th July and will participate in many charitable activities including visiting as a chief guest for a charity football match at Mohunbagan]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Argentina’s World Cup winning goalkeeper Emiliano Martinez on Monday confirmed on Facebook that he will be visiting Bangladesh in July.</p>



<p>Martinez wrote, “Hello Everybody, I will be doing my maiden trip to Indian subcontinent from 3rd July to 5th July and will participate in many charitable activities including visiting as a chief guest for a charity football match at Mohunbagan club, many fan engagement programs, sponsors felicitation and promote the beautiful game. I know Kolkata and Bangladesh has huge Argentina fans and I am very excited to meet them. Thank you Satadru for this initiative! Ami tomader bhalo bhashi!”</p>



<p>The news of Martinez’s trip to Dhaka was first broken in Bangladesh by Prothom Alo on 21 May. Martinez was approached by Indian sports promoter Satadru Dutta, who told Prothom Alo that he had initially approached Martinez for a trip to Kolkata.</p>



<p>The Argentinian goalkeeper then told him that he also wanted to visit Bangladesh. After that, Satadru started contacting potential sponsors in Bangladesh.</p>



<p>Martinez is expected to arrive in Dhaka on 3 July. He will stay in the Bangladesh capital for a day before heading to Kolkata the next day.</p>



<p>Martinez was a key figure in Argentina’s World Cup triumph in Qatar and became an instant favourite to the legions of Argentina fans across the world, including Bangladesh.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://watch.docnyc.net/argentina-world-cup-winner-martinez-confirms-bangladesh-tour/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Israelis revive flashpoint West Bank settlement</title>
		<link>https://watch.docnyc.net/israelis-revive-flashpoint-west-bank-settlement/</link>
					<comments>https://watch.docnyc.net/israelis-revive-flashpoint-west-bank-settlement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[International]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://watch.docnyc.net/?p=5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Israelis started reviving a flashpoint outpost settlement in the occupied West Bank on Monday, AFP journalists said, constructing a building at the site which has drawn international attention. Using a truck, diggers and an earth roller, work got underway to erect a portable building at the northern West Bank site. AFP journalists saw Israeli soldiers guarding around 20 people carrying]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Israelis started reviving a flashpoint outpost settlement in the occupied West Bank on Monday, AFP journalists said, constructing a building at the site which has drawn international attention.</p>



<p>Using a truck, diggers and an earth roller, work got underway to erect a portable building at the northern West Bank site.</p>



<p>AFP journalists saw Israeli soldiers guarding around 20 people carrying out construction work at the Homesh site, which Israel evacuated nearly two decades ago.</p>



<p>The latest development comes weeks after the office of Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu pledged his government had no plans to reconstruct the site, after a parliamentary vote on the matter sparked ire abroad.</p>



<p>It was hailed as a &#8220;moving historic moment&#8221; by Israel&#8217;s National Security Minister Itamar Ben-Gvir &#8212; an extreme-right settler.</p>



<p>Lawmakers in March voted to annul part of a law which banned Israelis from living in areas of the West Bank which the state evacuated in 2005, the same year Israel withdrew from the Gaza Strip.</p>



<p>&#8220;The government has no intention of establishing new communities in these areas,&#8221; Netanyahu&#8217;s office said in March.</p>



<p>Israel&#8217;s military occupation of the West Bank has been in force since the 1967 Six-Day War.</p>



<p>Neither the army nor the defence ministry commented on their role in Monday&#8217;s developments at Homesh when contacted by AFP.</p>



<p>The civilians at the site refused to discuss the matter when approached by AFP journalists.</p>



<p>The United States, Israel&#8217;s top ally, said this month it was &#8220;deeply troubled by the Israeli government&#8217;s order that allows its citizens to establish a permanent presence in the Homesh outpost&#8221;.</p>



<p>Washington and the wider international community view Israeli settlements built in the Palestinian territories as illegal and a barrier to peace.</p>



<p>The European Union last week pressed Israel to &#8220;cease the policy of settlement expansion&#8221; and condemned increased settler violence against Palestinians.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://watch.docnyc.net/israelis-revive-flashpoint-west-bank-settlement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
