<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>International &#8211; Doc Nyc News Today</title>
	<atom:link href="https://watch.docnyc.net/category/international/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://watch.docnyc.net</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:12:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://watch.docnyc.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOCNYC5100.png</url>
	<title>International &#8211; Doc Nyc News Today</title>
	<link>https://watch.docnyc.net</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Israelis revive flashpoint West Bank settlement</title>
		<link>https://watch.docnyc.net/israelis-revive-flashpoint-west-bank-settlement/</link>
					<comments>https://watch.docnyc.net/israelis-revive-flashpoint-west-bank-settlement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[International]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://watch.docnyc.net/?p=5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Israelis started reviving a flashpoint outpost settlement in the occupied West Bank on Monday, AFP journalists said, constructing a building at the site which has drawn international attention. Using a truck, diggers and an earth roller, work got underway to erect a portable building at the northern West Bank site. AFP journalists saw Israeli soldiers guarding around 20 people carrying]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Israelis started reviving a flashpoint outpost settlement in the occupied West Bank on Monday, AFP journalists said, constructing a building at the site which has drawn international attention.</p>



<p>Using a truck, diggers and an earth roller, work got underway to erect a portable building at the northern West Bank site.</p>



<p>AFP journalists saw Israeli soldiers guarding around 20 people carrying out construction work at the Homesh site, which Israel evacuated nearly two decades ago.</p>



<p>The latest development comes weeks after the office of Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu pledged his government had no plans to reconstruct the site, after a parliamentary vote on the matter sparked ire abroad.</p>



<p>It was hailed as a &#8220;moving historic moment&#8221; by Israel&#8217;s National Security Minister Itamar Ben-Gvir &#8212; an extreme-right settler.</p>



<p>Lawmakers in March voted to annul part of a law which banned Israelis from living in areas of the West Bank which the state evacuated in 2005, the same year Israel withdrew from the Gaza Strip.</p>



<p>&#8220;The government has no intention of establishing new communities in these areas,&#8221; Netanyahu&#8217;s office said in March.</p>



<p>Israel&#8217;s military occupation of the West Bank has been in force since the 1967 Six-Day War.</p>



<p>Neither the army nor the defence ministry commented on their role in Monday&#8217;s developments at Homesh when contacted by AFP.</p>



<p>The civilians at the site refused to discuss the matter when approached by AFP journalists.</p>



<p>The United States, Israel&#8217;s top ally, said this month it was &#8220;deeply troubled by the Israeli government&#8217;s order that allows its citizens to establish a permanent presence in the Homesh outpost&#8221;.</p>



<p>Washington and the wider international community view Israeli settlements built in the Palestinian territories as illegal and a barrier to peace.</p>



<p>The European Union last week pressed Israel to &#8220;cease the policy of settlement expansion&#8221; and condemned increased settler violence against Palestinians.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://watch.docnyc.net/israelis-revive-flashpoint-west-bank-settlement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
